in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create these technologically
您可以如何在技术上创建这些
styled letters that look like they're
带有样式的信件，看起来像是
made of circuits using nothing but
用什么都不用的电路制成的
strokes and shapes in inkscape so I'll
Inkscape中的笔画和形状，所以我将
come over here into a new document and
到这里来写一份新文件，然后
I'll get started the first thing I want
我要做的第一件事就是开始
to do is grab the rectangle tool and
要做的是抓起矩形工具并
click and drag on the cvas to draw a
在CBA上单击并拖动以绘制
rectangle I want to hold my control key
矩形我想按住Ctrl键
while I do that so we have a perfectly
当我这么做的时候，我们就有了一个完美的
symmetrical square like that then I'm
像这样对称的正方形，然后我就
going to remove the fill color from that
我要删除其中的填充颜色
rectangle by clicking this red X down
点击这个红色X向下的矩形
here in the bottom left corner and I
在这里的左下角，我
want to apply a black stroke to this
我想对此应用黑色笔触
object by holding the shift key and
通过按住Shift键和
clicking on the black Swatch down here
点击此处的黑色色板
in my color palette and now we have a
在我的调色板上，现在我们有一个
square with a black
黑色方块
outline so let's come over here to the
提纲，让我们到这里来
selection tool come up here to the tool
选择工具来到这里的工具
settings menu uh where this icon that
设置菜单呃这个图标在哪里
says when scaling objects scale the
表示在缩放对象时缩放
stroke width by the same proportion
笔划宽度按相同比例
let's turn that off for this tutorial
让我们在本教程中将其关闭
and now let's change the size of the
现在，让我们更改
stroke here so I'm going to open up the
在这里划，所以我要打开
fill and stroke menu by going to object
通过转到对象来选择填充和描边菜单
and selecting fill and stroke
并选择填充和描边
and from this menu I'll come over here
从这份菜单中，我会来到这里
to the stroke style Tab and I want to
添加到笔划样式选项卡，我想
make sure the stroke width is five
确保笔划宽度为五
pixels so mine's already set to five
像素，所以我的像素已经设置为5
pixels if yours isn't just manually type
像素，如果您的像素不是手动输入的
that in and change the units of
并改变其单位
measurement to pixels Here and Now I
此时此地对像素的测量
want to make this Square 100 by 100
我想把这个正方形变成100乘100
pixels so I'll come up here to the
像素数，所以我会来到这里
toolbar where we have the width and the
工具栏，我们在其中具有宽度和
height I'm going to turn on this lock
我要打开这把锁
icon between the two of them to make
他们两个之间的图标来制作
sure that we're locking the proportions
当然，我们正在锁定比例
as we scale and I'm going to change this
随着我们的规模扩大，我将改变这一点
to 100 and press enter and now we have a
设置为100并按Enter键，现在我们有一个
100 100 by 100 rectangle uh with a five
100个100乘100个矩形，呃，带五个
pixel
像素
stroke so what I'm going to do now is
所以我现在要做的是
I'm going to duplicate this I'm going to
我要复制这个，我要
right click this and go to duplicate and
右键单击此选项，然后转到复制和
I'm going to add 25 pixels to each
我将在每个像素上增加25个像素
Dimension so this one will be 125 pixels
大小，所以这个将是125像素
so I'll write in 125 and press enter and
所以我要写125，然后按Enter键
then I'll do this one more time I'll
那我就再来一次我会
right click this go to duplicate and
右键单击此转至复制并
I'll make this one 150 so I'll write in
我会把这个调到150，这样我就会写信给你
1 15 and press enter and there we go and
然后按Enter键，我们就可以开始了
now I'm going to select all three of
现在，我将选择以下三个选项
these and I just want to Center them up
这些，我只是想把它们放在中心
vertically and horizontally so I'll open
垂直和水平，所以我要打开
up the the alignment menu by going to
通过转到对齐菜单向上
object and selecting align
对象并选择对齐
distribute and from this menu I want to
分发并从此菜单中我要
choose last selected from this drop down
从此下拉列表中选择最后一次选择
and I'll Center them up vertically and
我会把它们垂直居中，
horizontally just like that so with all
在水平上就是这样，一切都是这样的
of these objects selected let's go to
在选定的这些对象中，让我们转到
path and select object to path so that
路径并选择要进行路径的对象，以便
now these are no longer rectangles these
现在这些不再是长方形了
are pure Vector paths and I'm going to
是纯向量路径，我将
grab my edit paths by nodes tool and I'm
抓起我的按节点编辑路径工具，我就
going to click and drag over these nodes
在这些节点上单击并拖动
over here on the right hand side to
在这里的右手边到
select them let me try that again if
选择它们，让我再试一次，如果
you're using Max sometimes it's
你在利用麦克斯有时这是
difficult to select these nodes there we
我们很难选择这些节点
go I was able to select those nodes now
Go我现在可以选择这些节点了
I'm going to come up here to the tool
我要到这里来拿这个工具
settings menu where it says add Corners
设置菜单，其中显示添加拐角
live path effect I'm going to enable
我要启用Live Path Effect
that and when I do that you're going to
当我这么做的时候，你就会
see these round knots that appear next
请看下面出现的这些圆形结
to the nodes and I'm going to select the
添加到节点，我将选择
nodes again and I'm going to grab this
再来一次节点，我要抓住这个
white node right here and just bring
白色节点就在这里，只要带上
this in like that until it snaps I want
就像这样，直到它断掉，我想
this I want it to snap right in the
这个，我想让它正好卡在
center there before you do that though
在你这样做之前，先把它放在那里
let me back up a little bit turn on your
让我倒回去一点，打开你的
snapping menu up here by clicking on
点击此处，点击此处的捕捉菜单
this mag magnet icon in the top right
右上角的磁铁图标
corner and then do that again so let me
转弯，然后再来一次，让我来
uh let me do that again now that I have
呃，现在让我再做一次，我有
snapping enabled and I want to snap them
已启用快照，我想要对它们进行快照
together just like that you'll see that
就这样在一起，你就会看到
red line up here there in the middle I'm
红线在中间，我是
going to do the same thing with these
我要用这些东西做同样的事情
other nodes over here I'm going to snap
其他节点在这里，我要抓拍
them together so we have nice rounded
他们在一起，所以我们有漂亮的圆形
edges like
边缘类似于
that and once we do that we can finalize
一旦我们做到了这一点，我们就可以敲定
this by going to path and selecting
这是通过转到路径并选择
object to path now with all with all of
立即将所有对象与所有对象连接到路径
these objects still selected I'm going
这些对象仍然被选中，我要走了
to select over all of these nodes right
要正确选择所有这些节点，请执行以下操作
here and I want to break all of them up
在这里，我想把它们全部分解
so I'll come over here to the tool
所以我会到这里来拿这个工具
settings menu and I'm looking for the
设置菜单，我正在寻找
option that says break path at selected
显示在选定位置断开路径的选项
nodes and when I click on that it's
节点，当我点击它时，它是
going to break them all up into separate
我要把它们都分解成单独的
nodes and now we want to break them up
节点，现在我们想要拆分它们
into separate objects so we'll go to
放入单独的对象中，因此我们将转到
path and select break apart and click
路径并选择断开，然后单击
off of the the graphic let's grab this
从图表上看，让我们抓住这个
selection tool and click off of it to
选择工具，然后将其关闭以
deselect everything and you can see we
取消选择所有内容，您可以看到我们
now have individual pieces of this
现在有了这些单独的片段
entire element here and if I select all
此处的整个元素，如果我选择全部
of these I can come over here to my fill
其中，我可以到这里来尽情享受
and stroke menu I could bring down the
和中风菜单，我可以把
opacity roughly in half and just so you
不透明度大致减半，这样你就可以
can see where the start and end point is
可以看到起点和终点在哪里
of each of these lines they all overlap
这些线中的每一条都有重叠
and underlap with each other and the
并相互之间和
point of doing this is that we now have
这样做的意义在于，我们现在拥有
these individual elements that we can
这些单独的元素，我们可以
use to construct virtually any letter
用来构造几乎任何字母
that we'd like so let me put that back
我们想要的所以让我把它放回去
and I'm going to zoom out I'm going to
我要缩小，我要
take all of these and I'm going to right
把所有这些都拿去，我要做正确的事
click them and go to duplicate and move
单击它们并转到复制和移动
the duplicate copy off to the side just
复印件正好放在一边
in case I want another copy to work with
以防我想要另一份副本
if I want to create other letters and
如果我想创建其他字母和
I'm going to use these objects right
我要正确地使用这些物品
here to to uh create the letter A so let
在这里，呃，创造字母A，所以让
me select all of them I'm going to
我要把它们全部选出来
rotate them around by clicking on the
通过单击
objects and then I'm going to get those
对象，然后我将得到那些
rotation handles and with the rotation
旋转控制柄和使用旋转
handles enabled I'm going to hold the
手柄已启用我要握住
control key and just roll it around
Ctrl键，然后滚来滚去
until it's flat like that and I'm going
直到它像那样平坦，我要走了
to create a letter A out of this right
在此基础上创建字母A
here I'll come back over here to show
在这里，我会回到这里来展示
you what I mean this letter a is what
你我的意思是这个字母a是什么
we're going to create so let me come
我们要创造，所以让我来吧
back into inkscape let me click off of
回到Inkscape，让我点击
it to deselect everything I'm going to
我要取消选择我要做的一切
click and drag over these three pieces
在这三个部分上单击并拖动
right here and I'm just going to bring
就在这里，我要带上
them up and I'm going to snap them up
把它们拿起来，我要把它们抢走
here I want this object to snap to this
在这里，我想让这个对象捕捉到这个
part of the uh the starting point of
部分，呃，起点是
that curve right there so I'll snap that
这条曲线就在那里，所以我要折断它
in
在……里面
there and now I want I want to make
就在此时，我想要我想要
these lines right here all the same
这些线条都是一样的
height so I want to take these lines and
所以我想用这些线条
bring them down so that they're the same
把他们拉下来，这样他们就是一样的
height as these ones with snapping
与这些带有捕捉的高度一样高
enabled we should be able to grab the
使我们能够抓取
nodes tool and select the node and then
节点工具并选择该节点，然后
just hold control and bring it straight
只要控制住它，让它直奔主题
down and it may
向下，它可能会
snap or we might have to create a guide
抓拍，否则我们可能不得不创建一个指南
for that so it didn't snap to the bottom
这样它就不会掉到底部
there what I'm going to do is I'm going
我要做的是我要去
to create a guide uh you should have a
要创建指南，呃，您应该有一个
ruler on your canvas up here if you
画布上的尺子，如果你
don't have a ruler uh as is the case on
没有尺子，呃，因为情况是这样的
my screen you can activate it by
你可以通过我的屏幕激活它
pressing control r on your keyboard or
按键盘上的Ctrl r或
if you're using Mac it would be command
如果您使用的是Mac，它将是命令
R and once we have that ruler we can
一旦我们有了尺子，我们就可以
click and drag a guide down here and I'm
点击并将向导拖到这里，我就
going to snap that Guide to the bottom
我要把这本指南翻到最下面
of this path right here and now I could
此时此刻我可以选择这条路
take these paths and snap them down to
选择这些路径并将它们捕捉到
the bottom of the guide and I'm holding
指南的底部，我拿着
control while I do this to lock the line
控件，同时我执行此操作以锁定行。
onto the vertical axis if I'm not
在垂直轴上，如果我没有
holding control it's going to wobble
握住控制权，它就会摇晃
around like that holding control will
像这样握住控制权就会
enable you to lock it onto that axis so
使你能够把它锁在那个轴上，这样
I'll come over here and do the same
我会来到这里，做同样的事情
thing I'm going to snap these lines as
我要把这些台词折断成
well and then I'm going to zoom back
好的，然后我要拉回
out and I'm going to adjust these lines
出去，我要调整这些线条
here so let me select this line in the
在这里，让我在
middle and I'm going to take this node
中间，我要把这个节点
and bring this in right here and I'm
把这个拿进来，我就是
holding control while I do that to lock
当我这样做以锁定时，我保持控制
it onto the horizontal axis I'm going to
我要把它放到水平轴上
bring that line right there and I'll do
把那条线拿到那里，我会做的
the same thing over here on this side
这边也是一样的东西
I'm just going to bring these lines in
我正要把这些线条放进来
like that and then I want to take this
就像那样，然后我想拿着这个
line right here and take this node and
就在这里排成一行，取下这个节点
just snap it down here and I'll do the
把它按下来，我来做
same thing over here on this side I'll
在这边也是一样，我会
snap this line onto this node and we end
将这条线连接到这个节点上，我们就结束了
up with this outcome right here so I'm
结果就在这里，所以我
going to get rid of the guide now I'm
我要除掉导游，现在我
going to make the guide Invisible by
要通过以下方式使向导不可见
holding shift and pressing the vert
按住Shift键并按Vert键
vertical Bar Key on the keyboard and I'm
键盘上的垂直条键，我是
going to get rid of the ruler as well
我要把尺子也扔掉
I'm going to press command r or controlr
我要按COMMAND或CONTROL
again to get rid of that and what we
再一次摆脱那个和我们
have here is we have all of these
这里有我们所有的这些
individual lines for each segment here
此处为每个线段的单独行
we want it to be one continuous path so
我们希望它是一条连续的道路，所以
for this segment here this is not a
对于此细分市场，这不是
continuous path this is broken up into
连续路径该路径被分解为
three pieces to make this a continuous
三个部分，使之成为一个连续的
path I'm going to select all of the
路径我将选择所有
objects by holding shift and clicking on
通过按住Shift键并单击
each of them and then I'll come over
他们每个人，然后我会过去
here to my nodes tool and I want to
这里是我的节点工具，我想
select all of these nodes I'm going to
选择我要访问的所有这些节点
hold shift while I'm doing that select
在我执行该操作时按住Shift键选择
all of the nodes and with them all
所有节点和所有节点
selected I'm going to come up here to
被选中的我将来到这里
the tool settings menu where it says
工具设置菜单，其中显示
join selected nodes and click on that
联接所选节点并单击该节点
and you can you should see that those
你可以你应该看到那些
overlapping segments go away we now have
重叠的部分消失了，我们现在有了
uh combined the nodes together so let me
呃，将节点组合在一起，所以让我
grab my selection tool if you notice we
抓住我的选择工具，如果你注意到我们
have a little bit of an extra piece that
有一点额外的东西
got left out here this is kind of like a
在这里被遗漏了这有点像是
I guess you could consider it a
我想你可以认为这是
mathematical error with working with
使用时出现数学错误
vectors it's really not supposed to be
向量它真的不应该是
there but it happens sometimes let me
但它有时会发生，让我
put that back if you have this on your
如果你身上有这个，就把它放回去
screen you could just select it and then
屏幕上您只需选择它，然后
press delete on your keyboard to get rid
按键盘上的Delete键即可删除
of it and now we're going to do the same
现在我们也要做同样的事情
thing to the rest of these paths we want
我们想要的这些路径的其余部分
this to be one continuous path as well
这也将是一条连续的道路
so I'm going to select each of these
所以我将选择其中的每一个
I'll come over here to my nodes tool
我会来到我的节点工具
I'll select each of these these nodes
我将选择这些节点中的每一个
one by one I want to make sure they're
我想要一个接一个地确保他们
all selected I'm going to hold shift
全部选中，我要按住Shift
while I do that to make sure they're all
我这样做是为了确保他们都
selected and I'll unify those together
被选中，我将把它们统一起来
as well and now I will do the same thing
我也是，现在我要做同样的事
to this line that runs in the middle so
到中间的这条线，所以
I'm going to hold shift and select each
我要按住Shift键并选择每个
of these lines and then I'll click and
然后我会点击并
drag over each of these nodes while
将鼠标拖到每个节点上，同时
holding shift to select all of them and
按住Shift键将其全部选中，然后
once I do that I'll merge them together
一旦我这样做了，我就会把它们合并在一起
as well now that's one continuous path
同样，现在这是一条连续的道路
and then finally I'll do that for this
最后，我会为这个做这件事
path as well so I'm going to select each
路径也是如此，所以我将选择每个路径
of these hold shift and click and drag
其中按住Shift键并单击并拖动
over each and then combine them
然后将它们组合在一起
together and there we go now we have
在一起，我们现在走到了一起
continuous paths for each segment of
每个网段的连续路径
this letter so at this point in the
这封信，所以在这一点上
tutorial we're going to start
我们将开始学习教程
subtracting areas of these lines and
减去这些线的面积，然后
adding the circles to the ends of them
将圆圈添加到它们的末端
to really complete this look here so let
为了真正完成这里的外观，所以让我们
me come back into here and we'll get
我回到这里，我们会得到
started on this uh I think at this point
从这个开始，呃，我想在这一点上
we can bring the opacity of these
我们可以把这些不透明的东西
objects back up let me select all of
备份的对象让我可以选择所有
them and bring the opacity back up to
并将不透明度恢复到
100% And I'm going to start off with
100%，我要从
this segment in the center here I'm
中间这一段我在这里
going to select that and grabb my nodes
我要选择它并抓取我的节点
tool and I want to add a couple of nodes
工具，我想添加几个节点
in an area where I'd like to subtract
在我想要减去的区域
part of the line so I'm going to double
一部分，所以我要加倍
click right here to add a new node and
单击此处添加新节点，然后
let's say I want to subtract the area or
假设我想要减去面积或
remove the line segment between these
删除这两个之间的线段
two nodes right here I could select both
这里有两个节点，我可以同时选择两个
of those nodes and I can come up here to
这些节点，我可以到这里来
the tool settings menu and select this
Tool Setting(工具设置)菜单并选择
option that says delete select delete
选项上写着删除选择删除
segment between two non- endpoint nodes
两个非端点节点之间的网段
and click on that and that line has been
点击这一点，这条线已经被
eliminated so I'm going to eliminate
淘汰，所以我要淘汰
another part of this line down here I'm
下面这条线的另一部分我是
going to double click to add a new node
要双击以添加新节点
right here and then double click to add
就在这里，然后双击以添加
a node right here and then I'll select
这里有一个节点，然后我将选择
both of those and I'll sub I'll uh
两个都要，我要代课，我要呃
subtract that segment as well and now
也减去那段，现在
what we can do is we can put the circles
我们能做的就是把圆圈
at the tips of those lines by coming
在这些线的顶端，通过来
over here to the stroke style Tab and if
在这里到笔划样式选项卡，如果
you notice we have these three drop
你注意到我们有这三滴水吗
downs for markers I'm going to choose
我要为记分器选择羽绒服
this drop down over here in the left
左侧的这个下拉列表
first I'm going to choose I'm going to
首先，我要选择，我要
click on that I'm going to choose this
点击我将选择此选项
rounded marker right here and I want to
圆角记号笔就在这里，我想
make the size of that 04 so by default
默认情况下将该04的大小设置为
it's 1.0 I'm going to remove that and
它是1.0，我要去掉它，然后
type in4 and press enter and I'm going
输入4，然后按Enter键，我将开始
to close out of that and I want to apply
结案，我想申请
the same type of marker to the end point
到终点的相同类型的标记
so I'm going to click on this drop down
所以我要点击这个下拉列表
and instead of choosing Circle again and
而不是再次选择Circle和
manually typing in that size we could
手动输入我们可以输入的大小
just use the most recently applied
只需使用最新应用的
marker so I'm going to choose this one
马克，所以我要选这个
right up here in the top of this list
就在这份名单的顶端
and now we have it applied there as well
现在我们也在那里应用了它
so the problem at this point is that we
所以现在的问题是我们
have the circles at the start point and
将圆圈放在起始点
the end point but we don't have them on
终点，但我们没有戴着它们
these middle points here so to fix that
这里的中间点，所以要解决这个问题
I'm just going to break this apart I'll
我只是要把它分开，我会
come up here and go to path and I'll
到这里来，走到小路上，我会
select break apart and now these are
选择拆分，现在这些是
separate segments that have the circles
分开带有圆圈的线段
at the start point and the end point of
在的起点和终点
each
每一个
line so now let's do the same thing down
现在让我们来做同样的事情
here with this other segment this time
这一次是另一段
I'm going to put the line braks on the
我要把线刹车放在
opposite side so instead of putting the
相反的一面，所以不是把
line break right here where it looks
换行符看起来就在这里
kind of symmetrical I'm going to make it
有点对称，我要把它做成
look a little little more Whimsical than
看起来有点异想天开
that so I'll put it over here I'm going
所以我把它放在这里，我要走了
to grab my nodes tool I'll double click
要获取我的节点工具，我将双击
to add a point right here and then I'll
在这里添加一点，然后我将
add another point right here and then
在这里再加一分
I'm going to select those and delete the
我将选择它们并删除
segment between between them and then
在它们之间分割，然后
I'll put another one down here I'll
我会把另一个放在这里，我会
double click this one and then put
双击此按钮，然后将
another one right there and I'll delete
另一个就在那里，我会删除
that segment out of there and now we can
现在我们可以把这一部分
just go to our markers drop down and
只要到我们的记分器下拉菜单
choose our previously used marker for
选择我们以前使用过的标记
each the uh for both the start and the
每一个都是，呃，开始和
end point and now we can break this
终点，现在我们可以打破这一切
apart by going to path and
通过去PATH和
selecting break
选择中断
apart and there we go that segment is
分开，我们走吧，那一段是
done now when I'm creating these letters
当我创作这些信件时，现在就完成了
what I like to do is I like to leave the
我喜欢做的是，我喜欢把
center line in place I don't like to
中线在我不喜欢的地方
break them apart and add those nodes on
将它们分开并添加这些节点
there because then it starts to look
因为然后它开始看起来
less like a letter I've noticed that
不像是一封信，我注意到
leaving that line like it is helps
让这条线保持原样是有帮助的
preserve its appearance as a letter
保留它作为字母的外观
especially if you zoom out more so let
特别是如果你缩小得更多，所以让
me Zoom back in and finally I'll do this
我放大，最后我要做这件事
outer line here so for this outer line
这是外线，这条外线是这样的
I'm going to put the line brakes at
我要踩下刹车
opposite sides of this one here in the
在这里，这一条的两边
center so instead of putting the line
居中，而不是把线
brake right here I'll put it over here
就在这里刹车，我会把它放在这里
so let me go back to my nodes tool I'll
让我回到我的节点工具，我将
click double click to add a node where I
单击双击以添加一个节点，其中
want the line brakes to be select both
我想要两种制动器都选
of them
其中之一
delete the segment and then I'll come
删掉片断，我就来
down here and do the same thing I'll
在这里做同样的事情，我会
maybe choose this part right here and
或许在这里选择这一部分，然后
then I'll just delete the segment
那我就把这个片段删除
between these two nodes let me try that
在这两个节点之间，让我试一下
again and then I'll delete that out of
然后我会把它从
there and again once again we could just
我们可以一次又一次地
choose the same markers for the start
为开始选择相同的标记
and end
和结束
point and then break it apart by going
指向，然后通过以下方式打破它
to path and selecting break
到路径并选择中断
apart and what I like to do is for this
分开，我喜欢做的就是为了这个
Center Line here I'm just going to grab
中线在这里，我只是要抓住
my nodes tool and I'm going to select
我的节点工具，我将选择
these two nodes and I'm just going to
这两个节点，我只是要
drag this down a little bit personally I
把这件事拖累一下，我个人
think this just looks a little better
我觉得这看起来好一点
when this Center Line descends down a
当这条中心线沿着一条
little further than those other two
比其他两个稍远一点
lines right there and as you can see
线条就在那里，正如你所看到的
we're finished with the letter now if
我们现在已经写完信了，如果
you want to change the color and style
您想要更改颜色和样式
of your letter you could just select
你可以从你的信中选择
over all of it and change the stroke
然后改变笔划
color so I'll come over here to the
所以我会到这里来
stroke paint Tab and I'll choose a new
笔划绘制选项卡，我将选择一个新的
color for my stroke that I've created
我为我的笔触创建的颜色
and there we go now we have a blue sort
好了，现在我们有蓝色的了
of line like that now one thing to keep
像这样的一条线现在有一件事要保持
in mind is because we have this setting
是因为我们有这样的设置
disabled if you go to scale this object
如果要缩放此对象，则禁用
up like that the lines are going to
就像这样，队伍就会变成
appear thinner and the same thing if you
看起来更瘦了，如果你
scale it down if you scale it down the
如果您按比例缩小，则按比例缩小
lines are going to appear thicker like
线条会看起来更粗，就像
that if you want to preserve the object
如果你想保留这个物体
so that it scales the line the line
这样它就可以将直线缩放到直线上
weight stays the same regardless of how
无论如何，重量都保持不变
much you scale it just enable this
你的规模很大，这就是实现这一点
setting again and now you'll be able to
再次设置，现在您将能够
scale your object however you'd like
随心所欲地缩放对象
without losing any of those proportions
而不会失去任何这些比例
and now you can repeat that process
现在你可以重复这个过程了
using these objects over here you could
在这里使用这些物品，你可以
take these lines and use them to create
取下这些线条，用它们来创造
every other letter of the alphabet and
字母表中的每隔一个字母和
I'll put a quick little graphic up on
我会在上面放一个快速的小图形
the screen here just to show you how I
这里的屏幕只是为了向你展示我是如何
went about creating all of the
着手创建所有的
individual letters of the alphabet if
如果是字母表中的单个字母
you want to use that for
你想用它来
inspiration and that should do it for
灵感，这应该会起作用
this tutorial as always thanks for
本教程一如既往地感谢
watching if you found this lesson useful
看看您是否觉得这堂课有用
then consider checking out my inkscape
然后考虑检查我的水墨景观
master class it's a collection of over
大师班这是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我回顾了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示
how they work kind of like how I did in
他们的工作方式有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人视频
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提问的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
并随时从我这里获得帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最重要的是没有每月
membership fees you just pay $17 one
会员费只需支付17美元一个
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间，你将迎来我将拥有的生活
some information about that down below
下面有一些相关信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地检查一下
thanks for
谢谢你
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
看